How can you do all this for your team's winning kids to
clean their match scene in
the morning, award winners and water, so he had
approached but he is very angry and he is not
digital, neither can pizza,
what will happen, if you take a better decision, then see, get involved, start small,
clean and
wash it, it will be difficult but it is
your duty to tell them,
guide them, give them direction and the
video is about that,
what do you need to tell teenagers, how can
real cider investment running
before committing suicide, yes Mahal, my name is
Cooling Coil Tikku, I bring a lot of wickets to that service, you MS
Word channel, every day so that
live TV can be made as per your and your choice, Idrish is the company's
line, we will do it, so without
video, many things we children do
not know in front, but actually they know, in the
background, I had done some videos last
year with those children, when I
asked them some personal account related questions, listening to their answers,
This will surprise them,
how to tell them all this and when they interviewed me,
if you want to
see the video, the links of which are in the description box,
please, with the family, one and a half inch, and somewhere or the other, you will
definitely find some people
from the milk unions, I was also surprised that they also know this word,
they also know this Financial Times, a
large section is very confident and their
thought process is, now
you should understand that if they should clean the maximum Johnny, then it is
religious and it is not that the
children will fold in the bar,
during this he had done his measurement sound very
quickly, 60, he had also said
that the festival doli switch on, a good job, the
foundation of the children is being made, show them the right way,
show them the right direction
so that they can clean their Bigg Boss Manjari,
if I make my tutorial, then what
happened earlier, parents usually used to put elements of a disease
of classification of the celestial
object in you
that money should be kept safe, so now that
time is not there, a bit  There has been a lot of change,
you have to tell
how we can do more groups than trees, you have to explain this to the children, if they want to
understand something and there is a possibility for the children too, then for
that, can we take cashless along,
first tell the children to set
up their funny bone, set their goals, for
example, I am from Leadership Sand Barwani, so
come now in 1974, that you very Hafiz, 16,
start shaving from Shiv, whatever gift money I got,
grandmother gave it, friend, from somewhere, suffering from
youth, festivals, she kept
using it everywhere and the appointments kept getting
delayed, when she had collected the money, she sat in the C
bottle, setting goals is very important,
setting targets
is very important, so tell the children to
set a timer, what is gold channel,
short term call 100 to three,
long term goals of children will also not be achieved, they will be able to
visualize the button, mid term poll and you have to
help them in that, now when they will be able to visualize, then
you know how much it costs, so
you can share this much  There is a need for the heart to understand the
importance of settings,
play the song, yes, think about investment
options because many times it happens that
children hear that this thing is available, this
share is available, 2018 tablet picture, so this
share is available, this frock is available, the
drama itself is cryptocurrency available, so
why should I do it here, why should I do it, friend, why should I do it, so
sit with them, brush your teeth, help them, get involved
with them, if you start small and even if you incur a loss, then nothing, if you learn something, then you will get complete, actually the information for the bride, only then will there be any benefit, so it is a very good thing, you sit and research with them,
see what investment options
are available, what are the things that can be of interest to
you, achievement creation, exploited
children, but take them for free
and like them,
apart from this, you can do it, what are the other possibilities,
and should you do it or not,
keep it in limited quantity
What will happen with this, the child also has to
change his/her Delhi Draft image son or daughter,
we have to make a video status that when you
message then definitely share it, you have seen
what happens in peace, if you want to
buy a phone then the whole family members will also ask what are the
features of this phone, what are the
specifications, how is the camera, how much RAM, how many
members are there, also how much is the real deal, how are all the
other features in appearance,
but no one is for an investment assistant, wastes so much
time in research,
so you also have to show this
poem to the children, become a role model, whatever you do, the children will follow
and in the same way they will
start their business, so you
sit with them in their seat and research this thing,
help the thoughtful, it
is available for opening an account at different places, to
open a demand account, here they have to
open an account in the bank or they have to do etc.
What is RD, explain voter
ID,
what is Systematic Investment Plan and
how can you activate it in this product,
where can you open an account, so like and
try to invest in their name only  You
can make impressions for this, you
can use rent everywhere, now I will
tell you, you can apply for PAN card and
send a reminder so easily, you can apply for Yagnik's
time advance in Margao to so Pankhuri,
you can open a text deposit in his name, you can
open a fixed deposit,
you can invest in mutual funds in his name,
so this can be done
in English as well in his name, so better
to-do list inside today also a distance
of ownership and when you get a call from a corner that
you invest anything as your duty, but doing it is
wrong, this is our money,
we have invested in this in our name and Manish Sood will take it,
and taking any
investment in last but not least, do as much
speculation as possible, do not let
children have a free hand in physical stocks *
with amendment, what are its benefits, what are its
disadvantages, in the long term,
especially cryptocurrency and other things, it
means if this Europe understands something, then we are
sitting and time
If you also do not understand about it then don't
speculate, don't do circulation that today the rate was so much,
now we should sell it for so much, this profit has been made,
then what is there in it, it will just
go into speculation mode, meter wide right hand
side effect circulation should never be done, if you do
good research
and invest in good companies then
avoid circulation, I
would like to raise an alarm,
tell the child about the benefits of compounding, tell the teenager about the benefits of compounding,
I have set the compounding so that the interest on
interest that you get on any
investment is flats of
duties and tagged corrupt and
vested interest, so peas become ₹10,
next year in the third year you will
get brinjal coin face of ₹10, so the
money will keep compounding like this, you will get interest on interest, so
tell about the benefits of compounding, this obscene be given to give vote,
so where will the small profits come from in the long term from compound interest  If we
invest in android2 for example 2013 by matching the mountain, then here I will
talk about the details, it makes 20% and
at ₹2000 I am starting the remaining 80 ml,
doing A, we need 2500 advantage, that is, make it
side by side length and it is a long ribbon,
so see, involve root for long term, so
toothpaste and mascara at ₹2000 and do it for 25 years
and if 20% return comes, then total
investment will be 160 rupees, simple maths
in 2012, 225 lakh rupees from this, it became 1.25 crore
rupees,
20% of interest rates are widely possible, if we
also see the pass performance, then it is quite
possible, from here it should be done on the left side
because focus on compounding benefit,
what will happen from this, there will be no speculation,
short term gain which is same worldwide game, that will
not come versus thought process, so
this will bring long term investment  If you want to
invest money for a long time, then this was
from my side that how can you help
voting, this is definitely a development journey, if there are any
questions in the city, please address the comment section
in the video, the parents, Suhaag cutting,
this and kidney, when you have children, share it with them,
share it with your teenage children,
they should understand the world, Hardik Nathuni
Sah, Ramesh Minjani, anything three times
in the comment section, our phone number
e-magazine is fine because from the doctor, also
and a reminder, if you have
not yet subscribed, please
subscribe, so that
you keep getting all such information at the right time, it is Android, till then stay tuned for the
next video
[Music]
[Music] do it